anallievent.com 2019-02-18

# Privacy & Disclosure Policy - An Alli Event

Privacy Policy of An Alli Event (https://www.anallievent.com)

You can contact me at anallievent@gmail.com.

**What information do we collect?**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. **You may, however, visit our site anonymously.**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may **opt out** of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

Personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

Improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

Send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We **do not** sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens’ Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s’ Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 05/17/2018

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support [help desk software](http://www.rhinosupport.com/).

**Disclosure**

I, Alli Smith, am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.
